

Hi! I'm Amie, 30-years old and from Lexington, Kentucky. In 2020 I zig-zagged my career into Graphic Design. I completed a full immersion UI course online through Career Foundry and began freelancing. My career goals are to freelance or work remotely while traveling. Although, I am currently still stationed at home in Lexington. I look forward to chatting with you about my portfolio and how I could benefit your team!

PHONE

859-339-2310

EMAIL

amieraeu90@gmail.com

SKILLS

Adobe: XD, Photoshop, Illustrator,

InDesign, Rush, Acrobat

Microsoft: Word, Excel, Power Point

AutoCAD

Google Sketch-up

Google Ads Social Media

Professional phone etiquette Clean and organized work ethic

Group communications

HOBBIES

Travel

Hiking

Art

Music

Yoga

Fashion

AMIE RAE UITTENBOGAARD

EDUCATION

Career Foundry, UI Design 2020-2021

I completed the online courses within 9 months. The extensive online courses include a full immersion into UI design. I focused on learning Adobe XD as well as extended my knowledge with other Adobe Creative software.

University of Kentucky, College of Design 2009 - 2014

Studio Coursework- 5 years: Environmental psychology, Finish materials, Color theory, Building systems, History of interior design and architecture, Digital media, Lighting design, and more.

Florence University of Arts, Florence, Italy Summer 2013

I chose to travel to Italy to experience its immense amount of historical value. I traveled to Rome, Tuscany, Florence, Venice, Cinque Terre, Capri, and Pompeii. I completed three weeks of coursework in Florence, which provided and abridged understanding of living abroad.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HDH Kitchen & Bath, Interior Designer August 2017 - July 2020

- Sole Interior Designer /Assistant for small local company in Lexington, KY
- · Worked directly with clients and contractors
- Acquired sales closing skills
- · Learned industry prices and budgeting for clients
- Honed skills on material selection and defining client aesthetic
- · Managed all marketing and social media

Amie Rae Designs & Garrard Wood Products, Laser Engraver Operator & Graphic Designer October 2014- August 2017

- In charge of running the ULS 6.60 laser engraver
- Required copious amounts of graphic design
- Engraved specifically bourbon barrel heads
- Created my own website
- Enjoyed working closely with clients to create custom designs

Coba Cocina, Server March 2013- June 2014

- Server in a high concept driven restaurant.
- Regarded by management as a key employee and assigned to train new hires
- Educate the guests on the theme of the environment
- Customer service requirement included providing customers a formal and hospitable dining